{
    "subject": "John_II_of_Aragon",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Juana_Enr\u00edquez",
    "human_readable": "John II of Aragon is married to Juana Enr\u00edquez.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9757251739501953,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the marriage between John II of Aragon and Juana Enr\u00edquez?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9362385272979736,
            "question": "What was the relationship between John II of Aragon and Juana Enr\u00edquez?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9289303421974182,
            "question": "To whom was John II of Aragon married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9009186625480652,
            "question": "Who was married to Juana Enr\u00edquez?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8343673944473267,
            "question": "Was there a historical connection between John II of Aragon and Juana Enr\u00edquez?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7723094820976257,
            "question": "Who is John II of Aragon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7604874968528748,
            "question": "Name the king who was married to Juana Enr\u00edquez."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6852940917015076,
            "question": "What is the name of Juana Enr\u00edquez's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3226107358932495,
            "question": "Who are some other figures who were important in the life of Juana Enr\u00edquez?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26241371035575867,
            "question": "What role did Juana Enr\u00edquez play in history?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=John II of Aragon is married to Juana Enr\u00edquez.",
            "html": "yago_22709_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some other figures who were important in the life of Juana Enr\u00edquez?",
            "html": "yago_22709_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Juana Enr\u00edquez's husband?",
            "html": "yago_22709_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the king who was married to Juana Enr\u00edquez.",
            "html": "yago_22709_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22709_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22709_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22709_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22709_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22709_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22709_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22709_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22709_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22709_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22709_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis answer indicates that the information in the documents supports the triple, meaning that John II of Aragon is indeed married to Juana Enr\u00edquez. This can be inferred from various mentions of Juana Enr\u00edquez as Queen Consort Aragon and her marriage to King Juan II of Aragon, which is explicitly stated in the document."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context information provided in the documents mentions that King Juan II of Aragon (John II of Aragon) was married to Juana Enr\u00edquez. This supports the statement that John II of Aragon is married to Juana Enr\u00edquez."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}